Hi! I'm John with expertvillage.com and we have our light switch plate cover and it's almost finished. All we have to do is seal it. Before we seal it, we can do a couple of other things.
We can add some paint and then let it dry and seal it. We can add some glitter. I am going to add some glitter.
It's going to be gold. You can just get this at any craft store. Before you go ahead and spray it, shake it up real good.
You don't want to do this in the house, but we're going to do it in the house anyway because we have an art room for this stuff.
Do it in your garage, out on the sidewalk, or whatever.
Just get something to put it on because it will over spray and get on your carpet or whatever.
Lay it on there.
We're just going to do a little bit.
When you do it, start out here, work in.
Even strokes.
The can's kind of empty.
That's okay.
I don't want to blast it with a bunch of glitter because it's going to be in my room, but I like it.
There's a little bit on there right now.
Let's let it dry, then we'll seal it.